Peter Fallon - Gallery Press collection, circa 1967-1998
Emory University
- Subject files, 1977-1996, Series 4; Boxes 167-176
  - Arts Council of Northern Ireland, Strategies, 1994-1995 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Association of Little Presses (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Awards - Aldenburgh Poetry Trust, 1991-1995 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Awards - Better Ireland, 1991-1994 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Awards - Better Ireland Awards (Box OP78)
  - Awards - Circa (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Awards - Forward Poetry Prize (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Awards - GPA Book Award (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Awards - Irish Book Design Awards, Award Certificates, 1977-1989 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Awards - Irish Book Design Award, Correspondence (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Awards - Irish Times Irish Literature Prizes (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Awards - Irish Times Irish Literature Prizes, 1991 Poster (Box OP79)
  - Awards - Misc. (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Awards - Patrick Kavanaugh Awards (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Awards - Poetry Book Society (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Awards - Poetry Ireland (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Awards - Poetry Society (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Awards - The Rooney Prize (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Bloodaxe Books - Correspondence (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Bloodaxe Books - Correspondence (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Bloodaxe Books - Promotional material (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Clé (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Colour Books, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Colour Books, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Colour Books, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Colour Books, 1994-1995 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Cork, Peter; Journey to the Arctic Shore, Publisher correspondence (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Cork, Peter; Journey to the Arctic Shore, MS (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Design (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Design - Eveleen Coyle (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Dublin Arts Festival (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Dufour Editions Catalogues, 1989-1993 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Festivals (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Festivals (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Festivals: International Festival of Authors, Harbourfest Centre, Toronto, Canada, 1995 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Festivals: Kells Heritage Festival, 1993-1994 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Field Day Anthology of Irish Writing (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Field Day Theatre Company (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Grant applications (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Irish Media Guide (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Irish Writers' Union (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Lawsuit - Derek McCabe (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Lawsuit - Sooner than Later Delivery Service (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Limerick Chair in Creative Writing (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - Lists (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - Meath Arts Group (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - Media/Publishers' Guides (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - National Lottery Fund (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - National Theatre Company / The Abbey Theatre (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Oldcastle Archaeological Historical Society (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Password, 1989-1991 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Password, 1994-1996 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Password - Catalogues (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Password - Misc. (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Poetry Ireland (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - The Poetry Society/National Poetry Centre (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Poets for Africa (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Power's Gold Label Short Story Competition (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Production (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Radio Telefis Éiran (RTE) (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Radio Telefis Éiran (RTE) Poet's Choice, 1982 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - School of Irish Studies (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - School of Irish Studies (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - School of Irish Studies (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Small Press Record of Books in Print (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Tara Telephone [Includes Poetry/Music Workshop sign-up book with dates from January 1969-December 1970] (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Tara Telephone/Peter Fallon Account and Bank Books (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Tara Telephone-- Engagement contracts (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Tara Telephone Publicity (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Tara Telephone - Capella Correspondence (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Tara Telephone - Capella Publicity (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Tara Telephone - Capella Submissions Correspondence (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Tara Telephone - The Book of Invasions (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Trinity College Higher Education (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Writer's Week (Box 176, Folder 9)
- Printed material, 1960s-1990s, Series 5; Boxes 177-193
  The series consists of printed material produced mainly by Gallery Press from 1960s-1990s. The materials include publicity files created for particular works published by Gallery Press, as well as general promotional materials for Gallery Press including catalogues, press releases and flyers for readings by authors. Also included general printed materials including newspaper clippings and catalogues of other publishers.
  Organized into three subseries: (5.1) Publicity files by authors, (5.2) Gallery Press promotional materials, and (5.3) General printed material.
  - Publicity files by author, Subseries 5.1; Boxes 177-186
    - Archer, Nuala (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Banville, John (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Banville, John - The Ark (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Banville, John - Broken Jug, The (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Banville, John - Ghosts (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Banville, John - Nightspawn (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Behan, Brendan (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Boland, Eavan (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Bourke, Ken - Wild Harvest (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Cannon, Moya - Oar (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Cannon, Moya - The Parchment Boat (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Carr, Marina (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Carr, Marina - The Mai (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Carson, Ciaran (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Carson, Ciaran - Belfast Confetti (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - Carson, Ciaran - First Language (Box 177, Folder 16)
    - Carson, Ciaran - The Irish for No (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Carson, Ciaran - Letters from the Alphabet (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Carson, Ciaran - The New Estate (Box 177, Folder 19)
    - Carson, Ciaran - Opera Et Cetera (Box 177, Folder 20)
    - Clifton Harry (Box 177, Folder 21)
    - Clifton Harry - Comparative Lives (Box 177, Folder 22)
    - Clifton, Harry - The Desert Route (Box 177, Folder 23)
    - Clifton, Harry - The Liberal Cage (Box 177, Folder 24)
    - Clifton, Harry - Night Train Through the Brenner (Box 177, Folder 25)
    - Clifton, Harry - Office of Salt Merchant (Box 177, Folder 26)
    - Clifton, Harry - The Walls of Carthage (Box 177, Folder 27)
    - Coady, Michael (Box 177, Folder 28)
    - Coady, Michael - All Souls (Box 177, Folder 29)
    - Coady, Michael - Oven Lane (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Coady, Michael - Two For A Woman, Three For A Man (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Davison, Philip - The Invisible Mending Company (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Dawe, Gerald (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Dawe, Gerald - Heart of Hearts (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Dawe, Gerald - The Lundys Letter (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Dawe, Gerald - Sheltering Places (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Dawe, Gerald - Sunday School (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Deane, Seamus (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Deane, Seamus - History Lessons (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Deane, Seamus - Reading in the Dark (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Deane, Seamus - Selected Poems (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Dunne, Seán (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - Dunne, Seán - The Sheltered Nest (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - Dunne, Seán - Time and the Island (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - Durcan, Paul (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - Durcan, Paul - Theresa's Bar (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - Ennis, John (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Ennis, John - The Burren Days (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Ennis, John - Dolmen Hill (Box 178, Folder 20)
    - Ennis, John - A Drink of Spring (Box 178, Folder 21)
    - Ennis, John - Night on Hibernia (Box 178, Folder 22)
    - Fallon, Padraic - Collected Poems (Box 178, Folder 23)
    - Friel, Brian (Box 178, Folder 24)
    - Friel, Brian - Aristocrats (Box 178, Folder 25)
    - Friel, Brian - Communication Cord (Box 178, Folder 26)
    - Friel, Brian - Dancing at Lughansa (Box 178, Folder 27)
    - Friel, Brian - The Enemy Within (Box 178, Folder 28)
    - Friel, Brian - Faith Healer (Box 178, Folder 29)
    - Friel, Brian - Fathers and Sons (Box 178, Folder 30)
    - Friel, Brian - The Freedom of the City (Box 178, Folder 31)
    - Friel, Brian - The Gentle Island (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian - Give Me Your Answer, Do! (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian - Living Quarters (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Friel, Brian - The London Vertigo (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Brian - Lovers (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Friel, Brian - The Loves of Cass McGuire (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian - Making History (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Friel, Brian - Molly Sweeney (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Friel, Brian - A Month in the Country (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Friel, Brian - Philadelphia, Here I Come! (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Friel, Brian - Selected Stories (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - Friel, Brian - Three Sisters (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Friel, Brian - Translations (Box 179, Folder 13)
    - Friel, Brian - Volunteers (Box 179, Folder 14)
    - Friel, Brian - Wonderful Tennessee (Box 179, Folder 15)
    - Gallery Press (Box 179, Folder 16)
    - Gallery Press (Box 179, Folder 17)
    - Glavin, Anthony - The Wrong Side of the Alps (Box 179, Folder 18)
    - Greacen, Robert - A Garland for Captain Fox (Box 179, Folder 19)
    - Grennan, Eamon (Box 179, Folder 20)
    - Grennan, Eamon - As If It Matters (Box 179, Folder 21)
    - Grennan, Eamon - So It Goes (Box 179, Folder 22)
    - Grennan, Eamon - What Light There Is (Box 179, Folder 23)
    - Grennan, Eamon - Wildly For Days (Box 179, Folder 24)
    - Groarke, Vona (Box 179, Folder 25)
    - Groarke, Vona - Shale (Box 179, Folder 26)
    - Hardie, Kerry (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Hardie, Kerry - A Furious Place (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Harnett, Michael (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Harnett, Michael - Collected Poems, vols. 1 and 2 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Harnett, Michael - Haicéad (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Harnett, Michael - A Farewell to English (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Harnett, Michael - The Killing of Dreams (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Harnett, Michael - A Necklace of Wrens (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Harnett, Michael - Ó Bruadair (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Harnett, Michael - Poems to Younger Women (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Harnett, Michael - Selected and New Poems (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Harvey, Francis (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Harvey, Francis - In the Light of the Stones (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Harvey, Francis - The Rainmakers (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Healey, Dermot (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - Healey, Dermot - The Ballyconnell Colours (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Heaney, Seamus (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - Heaney, Seamus (Box 180, Folder 18)
    - Heaney, Seamus (Box 180, Folder 19)
    - Heaney, Seamus - The Cure at Troy (Box 180, Folder 20)
    - Heaney, Seamus - The Government of the Tongue (Box 180, Folder 21)
    - Heaney, Seamus - The Haw Lantern (Box 180, Folder 22)
    - Heaney, Seamus - New Selected Poems, 1966-1987 (Box 180, Folder 23)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Nobel Prize (Box 180, Folder 24)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Nobel Prize (Box 180, Folder 25)
    - Heaney, Seamus - The Redress of Poetry (Box 180, Folder 26)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Seeing Things (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Heaney, Seamus - The Spirit Level (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Station Island and Sweeney Astray (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Hughes, John - The Devil Himself (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Hughes, John - Negotiations with the Chill Wind (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Hughes, John - The Something in Particular (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Hughes, Ted (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Hutchinson, Pearse (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Hutchinson, Pearse - Barnsley Main Seam (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Hutchinson, Pearse - Climbing the Light (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Hutchinson, Pearse - The Frost is All Over (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Hutchinson, Pearse - Selected Poems (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Hutchinson, Pearse - The Soul That Kissed the Body (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Hutchinson, Pearse - Watching the Morning Grow (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Jordan, John (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Kane, Michael (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - Kane, Michael - Art Exhibit (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - Kennelly, Brendan (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - Kilroy, Thomas (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - Kilroy, Thomas - Double Cross (Box 181, Folder 20)
    - Kilroy, Thomas - The Seagull (Box 181, Folder 21)
    - Kilroy, Thomas - Talbot's Box (Box 181, Folder 22)
    - Kinsella, Thomas (Box 181, Folder 23)
    - Longley, Michael (Box 181, Folder 24)
    - Longley, Michael - Poems, 1963-1983 (Box 181, Folder 25)
    - Lysaght, Seán - Clare Island Survey (Box 181, Folder 26)
    - McBreen, Joan (Box 181, Folder 27)
    - McCabe, Eugene (Box 181, Folder 28)
    - McCabe, Eugene - King of the Castle (Box 181, Folder 29)
    - McGuckian, Medbh (Box 181, Folder 30)
    - McGuckian, Medbh - Captain Lavender (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - McGuckian, Medbh - The Flower Master (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - McGuckian, Medbh - Marconi's Cottage (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - McGuckian, Medbh - On Ballycastle Beach (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - McGuckian, Medbh - Selected Poems (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - McGuckian, Medbh - Venus and the Rain (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - McGuiness, Frank - Booterstown (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Machado, Antonio (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - MacIntyre, Tom (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - MacIntyre, Tom - The Great Hunger (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - MacIntyre, Tom - The Harpers Turn (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - MacIntyre, Tom - Kitty O'Shea (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - MacIntyre, Tom - The Word for Yes (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - Magee, Heno (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - Magee, Heno - Hatchet (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - Mahon, Derek (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - Mahon, Derek - Antarctica (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - Mahon, Derek - The Bacchae (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - Mahon, Derek - The Chimeras (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - Mahon, Derek - Courtyards in Delft (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - Mahon, Derek - High Time/School for Wives (Box 182, Folder 21)
    - Mahon, Derek - The Hudson Letter (Box 182, Folder 22)
    - Mahon, Derek - The Hunt by Night (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - Mahon, Derek - Journalism (Box 182, Folder 24)
    - Mahon, Derek - Phaedra (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - Mahon, Derek - Selected Poems (Box 182, Folder 26)
    - Mahon, Derek - The Yaddo Letter (Box 182, Folder 27)
    - Mathews, Aidan (Box 182, Folder 28)
    - Mathews, Aidan - Exit/Entrance (Box 182, Folder 29)
    - Mathews, Aidan - Minding Ruth (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Meehan, Paula (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Meehan, Paula - The Man Who Was Marked by Winter (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Meehan, Paula - Pillow Talk (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Montague, John (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Montague, John - Collected Poems (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Montague, John - The Dead Kingdom (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Montague, John - Hill Field (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Montague, John - Mount Eagle (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Montague, John - Mount Eagle (Box OP80)
    - Montague, John - New Selected Poems (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Montague, John - The Rough Field (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Montague, John - Time in Armagh (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Muldoon, Paul (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Muldoon, Paul - The Annals of Chile (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Muldoon, Paul - Kerry Slides (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Muldoon, Paul - The Prince of the Quotidian (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - Muldoon, Paul - Six Honest Serving Men (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - Muldoon, Paul - The Wishbone (Box 183, Folder 18)
    - Murphy, Thomas (Box 183, Folder 19)
    - Murphy, Thomas - Bailegangaire (Box 183, Folder 20)
    - Murphy, Thomas - Conversations on a Homecoming (Box 183, Folder 21)
    - Murphy, Thomas - A Crucial Week in the Life of a Grocer's Assistant (Box 183, Folder 22)
    - Murphy, Thomas - Famine (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Murphy, Thomas - The Gigli Concert (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Murphy, Thomas - The Gigli Concert (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Murphy, Thomas - On the Outside/On the Inside (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Murphy, Thomas - Other Plays (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Murphy, Thomas - The Sanctuary Lamp (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Murphy, Thomas - Whistle in the Dark (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan - Acts and Monuments (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan - The Brazen Serpent (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan - Cork (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan - The Magdalene Sermon (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan - The Rose Geranium (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan - Second Voyage (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan - Site of Ambush (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala - Astrakhan Cloak (Box 184, Folder 17)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala, Other Works (Box 184, Folder 18)
    - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala - Pharaoh's Daughter (Box 184, Folder 19)
    - Nolan, Jim (Box 184, Folder 20)
    - Nolan, Jim - The Guernica Hotel (Box 184, Folder 21)
    - Nolan, Jim - Moonshine (Box 184, Folder 22)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor - History of Rain (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard - Poaching Rights (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - O'Donoghue, Gregory - Kicking (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - O'Grady, Desmond (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - O'Grady, Desmond - Sing Me Creation (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam - Dialann Bóthair (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Ormsby, Frank (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Ormsby, Frank - The Ghost Train (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - Ormsby, Frank - A Northern Spring (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - Ormsby, Frank - A Store of Candles (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - Parker, Stewart (Box 185, Folder 14)
    - Parker, Stewart - Catchpenny Twist (Box 185, Folder 15)
    - Parker, Stewart - Northern Star (Box 185, Folder 16)
    - Parker, Stewart - Pentecost (Box 185, Folder 17)
    - Reardon, Daniel (Box 185, Folder 18)
    - Rodgers, W.R. (Box 185, Folder 19)
    - Rodgers, W.R. - Poems (Box 185, Folder 20)
    - Simmons, James (Box 185, Folder 21)
    - Simmons, James - Poems, 1956-1986 (Box 185, Folder 22)
    - Sirr, Peter (Box 185, Folder 23)
    - Sirr, Peter - Ledger of Fruitful Exchange (Box 185, Folder 24)
    - Sirr, Peter - Marginal Zones (Box 185, Folder 25)
    - Sirr, Peter - Talk, Talk (Box 185, Folder 26)
    - Sirr, Peter - Ways of Falling (Box 185, Folder 27)
    - Smith, Michael (Box 185, Folder 28)
    - Sweeney, Matthew (Box 185, Folder 29)
    - Wheatley, David (Box 185, Folder 30)
    - Ais-Eiri vol. 3 no. 4 (Summer 1981) [Contains interview with Michael Hartnett] (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - An Gael (Summer 1994) [Contains "Above Board" short story by John Montague, p. 22; Review of Montague's The Dead Kingdom, p. 33; "Emigrant Huts" by Seán Dunne, p. 34; "Come Dance with Me in Irlaunde" essay by Ciaran Carson; Mention of Carson, Seamus Heaney, and Derek Mahon, p. 21] (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Comhar vol. 49 no. 1 (January 1990) [contains article about Liam Ó Muirthile; Ó Riordan review with mentions of Paula Meehan, Nuala Ní Dhómhnaill, and Medbh McGuckian; and "Slíoch" and "Al Fhéile Mhór" (translation) by Pearse Hutchinson] (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Driftwood Quarterly no. 1 [Contains "The Chauffeur Driven Rolls" by Roger McGough and "Poem" by Wes Magee] (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Drumlin (1995) [Contains multiple poems by Peter Moynagh] (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Exile vol. 11 no. 3 (1986) [Contains "Pilgrim's Pad" and "Contributors" by John Montague] (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Feasta Vol. 29 no. 9 (December 1976) [Contains review of The Frost is All Over by Pearse Hutchinson] (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - The Furrow (April 1974) [contains Gallery Press ad, p. 237] (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - The Honest Ulsterman no. 78 (Summer 1985) [Contains interview with Michael Longley; Reviews by James Simmons and Ciaran Carson; and article about Frank McGuinness] (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Gown Literary Supplement vol. 31 no. 4 (1985) [Contains interview with Seamus heaney; "the Day My Wife Purchased Herself a Hand-Gun" by Paul Durcan; "Porn" by John Hughes; "deirdre-A Fragment" by James Simmons; "The Libertion" and "the Flame Thrower" by Frank Ormsby; "Coleridge" and "April" by Medbh McGuckian; untitled Paul Muldoon poem; and review of Poems 1963-1983 by Michael Longley] (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - The Great Tuam no. 3 (1992) [contains "Veronica," "the photographs of my Aunts," "In a Suburban Garden on a Christmas Night," "Woman Herding Cattle in a Field near Kilcolgan," "Candles," "December" (translation), "Morning" (translation), and "Beyond" (translation) by Joan McBreen and "The Holy Medal Man" by Thomas Murphy] (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - Hitsville vol. 1 no. 8 (ca. 1969) [Includes article about B.P. Fallon with mention of Tara Telephone] (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Icarus 54 (1968) (Ní Chúilleanáin, Chairman) [Photocopy, original in Rare books collection] (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - Icarus no. 69 (Spring 1976) [Review Written by Eileán Ní Chuilleanáin, p. 41; review of Ní Chuilleanáin's "Site of Ambush," p. 43] [Photocopy, original in Rare books collection] (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - Martello (Winter 1992) [Contains "The Old Catechism" by Michael Hartnett (with handwritten corrections by PF); "Some Memories of Michael McLaverty (1904-1992)," essay by Robert Greacen] (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - Move no. 8 [April 1968] [Contains "Following in the Footsteps" by Wes Magee] (Box 186, Folder 16)
    - New Poetry no. 33 (1976) [Ad for A Garland for Captain Fox by Robert Greacen, p. 19] (Box 186, Folder 17)
    - North no. 3 (October 1984) [Contains reviews of Station Island by Seamus Heaney; Venus and the Rain by Medbh McGuckian; The Wishbone by Paul Muldoon; and High Time by Derek Mahon. Also contains "comrade Ted" by Robert Greacen]] (Box 186, Folder 18)
    - North no. 4 (Winter 1985) [contains "Mad Sweeney's Vision of Ulster" (poem) and novel extract by James Simmons; "News from Home" by Frank Ormsby; "Graveyard" by Desmond O'Grady; "The Barbecue" and review of Norman Mailer book by John Hughes; Edna Longley article about Patrick Kavanagh; John Hewitt interview talking about W.R. Rodgers; review of Marginal Zones by Peter Sirr; review of The Dead Kingdom by John Montague; and reviews of plays by Stewart Parker] (Box 186, Folder 19)
    - P & T: la regue culturelle (Japan, 1995) [Contains English originals and Japanese translations of "La Toilette," "Old Smoothing Iron," and "nesting Ground" by Seamus Heaney and an article (in Japanese) about Heaney by Michael Hartnett (?)] (Box 186, Folder 20)
    - The Pleiades will weep over Douglas Hide [Summer 1972] [Contains "June 1972" by Paul Durcan, "Where are all the Flowers Gone?" by Pearse Hutchinson, "The President's Birthday" by Patrick Kavanagh, "A Note on Yeats and Kavanagh" and "To my Table" by Brian Lynch, and "Soledades" by Michael Smith (Translated from the Spanish of Antonio Machado)] (Box 186, Folder 21)
    - Priapus no. 14 (Spring 1968) [Contains "The Windmill Hill People" by Wes Magee (Box 186, Folder 22)
    - Quickest Way Out no. 1 (ca. 1969) [Contains poem by James Simmons] (Box 186, Folder 23)
    - Resurgence vol. 2 no. 12 / New Departures 5 (Joint Issue) (Spring 1970) [Contains "The Holiday and After" by Wes Magee] (Box 186, Folder 24)
    - Scottish International Vol. 6 No. 2 (February 1973) [Contains review of Goodbye Schooltie by Brian McCabe] (Box 186, Folder 25)
    - "Wiparound" (Newsletter of Women in Publishing), Vol. 2 (1986) [Contains mentions of Eavan Boland and Frank McGuinness] (Box 186, Folder 26)
  - Gallery Press materials, Subseries 5.2; Boxes 187-189